...Insightful as ever, Eftirvit
I always find our discussions so rewarding
It's just food for thought. Could be nothing
After all, follow the logic through, and you are forced into some absurd conclusions...
With the means to summon the essence of a complex system, the process to extract Azosite
And technology developed to capture shooting stars...
We may actually be able to traverse space and defy gravity...
But that's the exciting part! My friend...
If this theory holds, we may one day be able to summon the essence of Celestia itself
Of course, there are plenty of technical issues to resolve first...
We'd also need a king ambitious enough to permit it
Your conclusion is by no means absurd
All of spacetime is intimately connected, and a rigorous theory is like magic in a scholar's hands
Professor, your health...
Today is a good day. I'm feeling much better
Thank you for your concern, Eftirvit
I'm so happy to see you, Professor Mimameith
We've missed having your input at the recent seminars under the tree. It's a pity
Hehe, it's no great loss
There is very little left that I can teach you
In the future, I am sure you will be the very top scholars in this whole nation
My only hope is that I might live long enough to see the future you create
How is Professor Mimameith? I heard you went to see her
Her condition has visibly deteriorated...
Medical treatment has no effect, nor do more direct methods of extending her lifespan. It makes no sense
There's only one explanation... Chronic complications from His Majesty's research project
Her health was never the same after she returned...
You mean the Abyss project?
Yes
I won't give up. There has to be a way...
Professor Mimameith has always treated us like family. Whatever it takes, we must save her
I'll use all resources at my disposal. Some of the research at the Universitas could be promising
Uh, and about my promotion to president... I hope there's no—
Hey, there's a time and a place. This is not it
...You're right. My mistake, sorry... We should focus on the professor for now
You've found a way?
Yes. Mystery solved...
As you know, I've been leading research into the Crimson Moon
Recently, I discovered a more fundamental approach to extending lifespan...
How feasible is it? How does it differ from all the previous failed methods?
This suddenly feels like a seminar under the tree, Eftirvit
With your incisive questioning... we made so much progress back then
But let's not waste time on theory. The results will be all the proof we need
After all, the professor doesn't have much time left...
Very well. I trust you, Hroptatyr
I question only the theory, not your abilities
Thank you, Eftirvit
With this development, even His Majesty will be amazed
Now, I simply deconstruct the Crimson Moon's power, and the professor will...
What is it, Hroptatyr? What are you waiting for?
It... won't work
The theory is flawed. I was mistaken
...You're lying. You never doubt yourself, Hroptatyr. Explain yourself!
It's nothing. I'll find another way. Sorry about this
Are you worried I'll steal your work!?
However jealous I may be of your career, I would never do such a thing!
Our professor's life is at stake here!
Hroptatyr! Wait...!
Watch out, it's going to rain